{
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "Which animal lays eggs?",
      "choices": ["Dog", "Cat", "Duck", "Sheep"],
      "rightanswer": "Duck"
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "A male cow is called?",
      "choices": ["Ox", "Dog", "Sheep","Monkey"],
      "rightanswer": "Ox"
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": " All animals need food, air, and ____ to survive.",
      "choices": ["House", "Water", "Chocolate4"],
      "rightanswer": "Water"
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "What is Earthâ€™s only natural satellite?",
      "choices": ["Sun", "Mars", "Moon"],
      "rightanswer": "Moon"
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "Frozen water is called",
      "choices": ["fog", "ice", "steam"],
      "rightanswer": "ice"
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "The tree has a branch filled with green _____.",
      "choices": ["Root", "Leaves", "Trunk"],
      "rightanswer": "Leaves"
    },
    {
      "id": "7",
      "question": "The two holes of the nose are called?",
      "choices": ["Nostrils", "Eyelids", "Nails"],
      "rightanswer": "Nostrils"
    },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "What star shines in the day and provides light?",
      "choices": ["Venus", "Moon", "Sun"],
      "rightanswer": "Sun"
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "What part of the body helps you move?",
      "choices": ["Eyes", "Lungs", "Muscles"],
      "rightanswer": "Muscles"
    },
    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "Legs have feet and arms have ___.",
      "choices": ["Hands", "Pelvis", "Ankles"],
      "rightanswer": "Hands"
    }
  ]
}
